featurepics.com 2009-06-19

# FeaturePics.com - stock photography : royalty free, rights-managed photos. Privacy Policy.

**In the growing digital imaging market, FeaturePics offers:**

  * Transparency. What you see is what you get, no hidden fees. 
  * Savings for you. Our images are reasonably priced to fit your budget. 
  * Intuitive image searching to ensure you to find exactly what you need, and easily. 
  * Responsive communication with you. We take pride in providing the best support to our clients. 
  * Wide range of images, both Royalty Free and Rights Managed. 
  * Appreciation for our artists. Our artists receive 70% commission. This enables our artists to price their images competitively and pass on the savings to you. 

**What we do for Buyers and Contributors:**

  * Sell image licenses for the price quoted. No hidden fees. 
  * Sell not only Royalty Free Image Licenses, but Rights Managed Image Licenses as well. 
  * Appreciate our Contributors. All photographers receive a 70% commission rate. 

Please check our stock images at FeaturePics.com 

| 

| **FeaturePics Privacy Policy**  
---  
We value your business and respect your privacy. This is our Contract with you when you submit information online:
* We will never rent, sell or share information that personally identifies you for marketing purposes  

* Your participation is completely voluntary. You can update your account information whenever you desire  
We continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features we provide. For that reason, we encourage you to review the privacy policy periodically, because this policy is subject to change without prior notice. By using our Web site, you agree to the terms of the privacy policy, so if you see something you don't like, let us know.   
Information that we gather   
**1\. Registration for Artists:**  
Registration is optional, you don't need to register to browse. However if you browse our site, and decide to upload images, download images, leave messages or requests, you must be a registered member.   
_Email Logon:_ This is your unique identification to logon.  
We will send you an e-mail confirming your registration on our site, and in the event you forget your password, we will send it to your e-mail address at your request.   
Occasionally, we will send notification e-mails (for example: your images have been requested, or you have email requests from buyers etc.). You can opt-out of this option if you don't want to receive FeaturePics notifications when you edit your account preferences.   
_First Name/Last Name:_ We require your first and last names to help us differentiate your registration profile from others at www.FeaturePics.com.   
_Phone (with area code):_ We don't require a phone number. However, if you chose to provide it we may call you and ask for additional information on behalf of our qualified buyers. Again, here the privacy policy is strictly enforced.   
_Mailing Address:_ We require a mailing address in order to send you checks, 1099 forms, invoices, and any other information that we feel you may need. There will be no advertisements mailed to you.   
**2\. Online Ordering Information**  
_Email Logon:_ This is your unique identification to logon.  
We will send you an e-mail confirming your registration on our site, and in the event you forget your password, we will send it to your e-mail address at your request.   
Periodically, we will send newsletters (approximately once a month). You can unsubscribe from our mailing list by using the "unsubscribe" link on the bottom of each newsletter.  
  
_Billing address:_ Your billing address is required to submit for credit card verification   
_Credit Card Details:/_ We don't keep credit card numbers in our system; we do retain the last four digits for reference.   
Use of cookie technology   
You must enable cookies on your web browser for FeaturePics.com to function correctly. Only Session cookies are required. We don't collect personal information. Our cookies cannot read data from your computer, nor do we do any form of tracking.   
Identifiable information from children under the age of 13   
To comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act, at this time, FeaturePics will only be available to users who are at least 13 years of age or older. If you are under 13, please do not use the FeaturePics service. Please do not allow children under the age of 13 to provide any personally identifiable information to our Web site. If we determine that a child under 13 has provided personal information in violation of this policy, we will delete that information as soon as possible. If you become aware that such information has been provided by a child under 13, please send us an e-mail at [contact@FeaturePics.com](mailto:contact@FeaturePics.com) so we can delete this information.   
External Links   
Feature Image sometimes provides links to Web sites outside of FeaturePics as an added convenience to the user. Any link included does not imply or convey endorsement of the site or its products or services. FeaturePics is not responsible for the privacy, politics, terms of use, or other policies (tracking or otherwise) of any other Web site.   
EFFECTIVE 10/15/05
